Guide to the Lesbian and Gay Liberation Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional material, 1948-2010; Accession 2012-M-030
  - Plays and theater companies, 1959-2008
    - With the Greatest of Ease, Robert Michael Productions [program], Circa 1986 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Pride marches, 1979-2005
    - California - Los Angeles, 1982-1996 (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
    - California - San Diego, 1991-1999 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - California - San Francisco, San Jose, Santa Cruz, Northern California, West Hollywood, 1991-2005 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Georgia - Massachussetts, 1984-1999 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Minnesota, 1991-2003 (Box 4, Folder 4-5)
    - Nevada - New York, 1984-2002 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Ohio - Washington, D.C., 1979-2004 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Australia and France, 1989-2003 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Film catalogues, 1980-2007
    - Charis Video: The Lesbian and Feminist Video Resource, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Frameline 1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Frameline Distribution Film and Video Catalogue, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Frameline Distribution Film and Video Catalogue Supplement, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Iris Films, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Picture This! Home Video, 2005 summer (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - TLA Video, "Summer 1996 Gay and Lesbian Film Catalogue" (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - TLA Video, "Winter 1998-99 Gay and Lesbian Film Catalogue", 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - TLA Video, "Spring 2001 Catalogue" (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - TLA Video Catalogue 223: Holiday 2007 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Women Make Movies, "1994 Film and Video Catalogue" (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Women Make Movies, "1997 25th Anniversary Film and Video Catalogue" (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Film festivals, events, and newsletters, 1976-2008
    - Campus Theatre
      - "Nothing Turns You On Like Spanish Fly! Carlos Valentino" [flyer], 1988 June (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - "Tropical Heat Wave! Brazil's Hottest Male Erotic Superstar, Vladimir Correa" [flyer], 1988 May (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Castro Theatre calendar, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Chicago Lesbian and Gay International Film Festival, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Cinemattachine
      - "Happy Bicentennial New Year!" [flyer], 1976 January (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - "Jock Nights" [flyer], Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Close-up: Visionaries of Modern Cinema, Presented by Frameline [flyer], 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - "Cute Girl Party: Honoring the Women Filmmakers of Frameline 29" [flyer], Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Daily Flyer, San Francisco, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      This is Volume 1, Number 3.
    - "Erotic Films by James Broughton and Joel Singer, Banned in St. Louis, Censored by PBS" [flyer], Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - "Falcon Brand" advertisement, Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Fame [newsletter], 1988 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      This is No. 145.
    - Festival de Films Gays and Lesbiens de Paris, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Festival de Films Gays and Lesbiens de Paris: Films de Tous les Genres, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Festival Genres d'A Cote: Pinks Screens, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Festival International de Films Question de Genre: l'Homosexualite a l'ecran, Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Festival Les Bisqueers Roses: C'est Question Genre?, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Festival Question de Genre: Sexes & Ecritures, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Festival Question de Genre 5, Programme, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Framelines [newsletter], 1984 fall (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Framelines [newsletter], 1984 spring (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Frameline, "Buddies World Premiere", 1985 fall (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Frameline, "Frameline to Celebrate 10th Anniversary" [newsletter], 1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Framelines, 1985 winter (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - "Frameline and the Annual San Francisco International Lesbian and Gay Film Festival Are Growing..." [pamphlet], 1997 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Gay USA: A Film Tribute to Arthur J. Bressan, Jr., Castro Theatre, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Hong Kong Lesbian and Gay Film Festival, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - "Immaculate Conception: Films by Marc Huestis" [flyer], Circa 1980 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - "Joan Collins Film Tribute" [flyer], Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - "Joan Collins Film Tribute, Castro Theatre" [flyer], 1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - "John Waters Film Festival, Castro Theatre" [flyer], Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Lesbian and Gay Film Festival, Pittsburgh Filmmakers, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - "Lesbian / Gay History / Representation: An historically oriented lesbian / gay film series at the University of Chicago's DOC films", 1992 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - L.A. International Gay and Lesbian Film / Video Festival, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Los Angeles International Gay and Lesbian Film and Video Festival, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Los Angeles Internation Gay and Lesbian Film and Video Festival, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Los Angeles International Gay and Lesbian Film and Video Festival, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - L.A. International Gay and Lesbian Film and Video Festival, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Los Angeles Gay and Lesbian Film Festival: Outfest 98, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Mezipatra: Czech Gay and Lesbian Film Festival, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - NAMBLA Film Festival, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - New Conservatory Theatre Center Millennium Pride Season: Sex, Guts, Glory, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - New York International Festival of Lesbian and Gay Film, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - New York International Festival of Lesbian and Gay Film, Festival catalogue, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - New Queer Cinema, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - New York Gay Film Festival, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - New York International Festival of Lesbian and Gay Film: Decent Exposure, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - New York Lesbian and Gay Film Festival, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - NY Lesbian and Gay Film Festival, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - No Secret Anymore: The Times of Del Martin and Phyllis Lyon: A World Film Premier Celebrating Their 50th Anniversary, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Reeling Summer Film Festival: A Gay Games VII Affiliated Event, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Pikes Peak Lavender Film Festival, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Queer Weekend, Presented by Melbourne Queer Film and Video Festival, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - "Remember TV? Nocturnal Dream Shows" [flyer], Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - "San Francisco Familiar, Natoma Film Society" [flyer], Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - San Francisco Gay Film Festival, Circa 1980 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - San Francisco Interntional Asian American Film Festival: Queer Works [flyer], 1997 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - San Francisco International Documentary Festival: Indie Fest, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - San Francisco International Lesbian and Gay Film Festival, 1981-2005 (Box 6, Folder 1-4)
    - "Secret Cinema: Nocturnal Dream Shows" [postcard], Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Six of One / Half-dozen of an Other: Reflections of Lesbians and Gay Men, a Film Festival, Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Southwest Gay and Lesbian Film Festival, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - "SMTFS" [flyer], Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - "Spunked: Stupid Gay Party Tricks, the Complete First Load" [postcard], 2005 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - "Strand" [flyer], 1988 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Teddy 22: Queer Film Award, Internationale Fimfestspiele Berlin, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Tranny Fest [program schedule], Circa 1998 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - "Turin International Gay and Lesbian Film Festival" [postcard], Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - "Tri-Image Productions" [flyer], 1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Women's Video Festival NYC, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - "Word Is Out: Stories of Some of Our Lives" [flyer], Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - "Word Is Out! A Party by The S.F. Gay Teachers" [flyer], Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Movies and television shows, 1979-2005
    - Before Stonewall: The Making of a Gay and Lesbian Community, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Beyond Lovely, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Bike Boy, Castro Theatre [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Billy's Hollywood Screen Kiss [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Breaking the Surface: The Greg Louganis Story, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Call Me Malcom [flyer], 2004 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Caravaggio [flyer], 1986 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Chan Is Missing, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Chelsea Girls [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - "Choosing Children: A New Film about Lesbians Becoming Parents" [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Creep [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Cruising [protest flyer], 1979 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Cruising [protest flyer], 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Dare [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Day One: A Period Piece [flyer], 2005 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Deliriously Jen: Taking Oblivion to the Next Level [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Dick: A Film [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Ernesto [flyer], Circa 1979 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - For a Lost Solider [review], 1993 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Funny Kinda Guy [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Fur on Fire [press release], 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Gay USA, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Gay USA complimentary ticket, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - "Gay USA: Tenth Anniversary of Its Triumphant Premiere, A Film Tribute to Arthur J. Bressan, Jr." [flyer], 1987 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Getting to Know You [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Greetings From Washington, D.C., 1981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - "Harvey Milk Film Project", 1984 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - "Harvey Milk Film Project: Photograph Release", 1984 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - "James Broughton" [curriculum vitae], Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Healing Sex [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Hoi Maya [flyer], 2004 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Hope Along the Wind: The Life of Harry Hay [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - In a Year of 13 Moons [review], 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - In the Life, PBS, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Licking Our Wounds [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Life in a Box [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Making Love, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - My Brother Nikhil, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Myopia [flyer], 2005 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Myra Breckingridge [flyer], 1982 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Never Rob a Bank with Someone You Love [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Nighthawks [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Nineteen Eighty Four Lesbian-Gay Parade [flyer], 1984 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - On the Low [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Out of Order [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Outrageous! [photograph], Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - "Passion of Words Turning Into Action: A Black Deaf Filmmaker's Journey" [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Peter Berlin: A Documentary [flyer], Circa 2005 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Ping Pong Love [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Poison by Todd Haynes, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Pre-Code Hollywood [flyer], 1999 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - P4W: Prison For Women [flyer], Circa 1982 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Private Lessons [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Project 36-C, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Psycho Beach Party [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Race You to the Bottom [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Saint Henry [flyer], Circa 2004 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Same Sex America [flyer], 2005 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Sancharram: The Journey [flyer], 2005 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Sandstone [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Screaming Queens [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Sex, Politics, and Cocktails [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Show Me [flyer], 2004 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Siren Island [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Surge of Power: The Stuff of Heroes [flyer], 2004 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Surge of Power [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Taco Chick and Salsa Girl [flyer], 2005 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Taxi Zum Klo, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - The Captive [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - The Castro: Part Three of Neighborhoods, The Hidden Cities of San Francisco, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - The D Word [flyer], 2005 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - The Front Runner, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - The Joy of Life [flyer], 2005 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - The Times of Harvey Milk, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - The Times of Harvey Milk, San Francisco premier, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - The Times of Harvey Milk [flyer], 1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - The Times of Harvey Milk [flyer], 1984 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - The Trials of Oscar Wilde [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - The Watermelon Woman, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Tricks [flyer], Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - We Are Dad [flyer], 2005 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Whatever Happened to Susan Jane? [flyer], 1982 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Whatever Happened to Susan Jane? [flyer], 1982 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Whatever Happened to Susan Jane? [flyer], 1981 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Windows, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Women in Love [flyer], 2005 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Zero Degrees of Separation [flyer], 2005 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Musical concerts, performances, and dances, 1977-2006
    - A Decade of Pride, Lesbian/Gay Chorus of San Francisco, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - A Decade of Pride, Lesbian/Gay Chorus of San Francisco [program], 1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "A Gala Chorus Preview" [program], 1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - A Gay Musical Celebration at Davies Symphony Hall, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "A Halloween Mascquerade Ball" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - A Musical Celebration at Grace Cathedral [program], 1979 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - A Musical Celebration at Grace Cathedral [pamphlet], 1979 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - A la Carte: San Francisco Gay Freedom Day Marching Band and Twirling Corps In Concert [program], 1982 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - A Pair of Busts [flyer], 1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "A Season of Note" [flyer], 1981 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - A Star Spangled Night for Rights [program], 1977 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - A Superband Concert [program], 1979 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "An Evening of Mellow Jazz" [flyer], 1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "An Evening of Music and Poetry" [flyer], 1982 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - A Whole Lot of Bessie In Me [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "Adams-Currens, Hawley: Electric Violin" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "All I Need for Christmas" [flyer], 1982 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - At My Place, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "Athens Boys Choir" [pamphlet], Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "Avalon Boulevarde" [flyer], 1981 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "B Street Playlist", 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Back to Our Roots, San Francisco Gay Men's Chorus [program], 1994 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "Bay Area Women's Philharmonic: Sharon Isbin Classical Guitar" [flyer], 1983 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "Bay Area Women's Philharmonic Inaugural Season" [flyer], 1982 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "Benefit by the Bay for the SF Lesbian Gay Freedom Day Parade" [flyer], 1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "Blackberri: Finally!" [flyer], 1982 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Bobby Sox to Beatles [program], 1991 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Book of Love [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "Butch Wax Records: Scandal in the House" [flyer], 1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "Bythell, Cynthia, 'Christmas Time is Here by Golly, Disapproval Would Be Folly'" [flyer], 1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Canteen [flyer], 1984 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Canteen [flyer], 1983 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Catch a Rainbow! A Full Spectrum of Choral Music [program], 1985 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Celebrating Stonewall [program], 1994 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Closet Ball [program], 1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Colors of Contribution [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "Dance and Party!" [flyer], 1995 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Dance Dance Dance: In San Francisco" [pamphlet], Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Dance! Dance! Dance! Music by Disco Inc." [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Dancing, "Ballroom and Latin Dancing for Lesbians and Gay Men" [flyer], 1988 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Dancing, "Components of Ballroom / Latin Dance for Lesbians and Gay Men" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Dancing, "Couple-Dancing for Gay Men" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Dancing, "Country and Western Dance" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Dancing, "Country Western Dance: A Fundraiser in Support of 'Our Common Welfare'" [flyer], 1990 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Dancing, "Dance Tango" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Dancing, "Queer Ballroom, Queer Salsa, Queer Swing!" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Disappear Fear Reunion Concert" [pamphlet], 2000 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "De-mystifying the Recording Process, June Millington and Tret Fure" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Die Tageszeiten, San Francisco Gay Men's Chorus [program], 1985 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - DiFranco, Ani, Circa 1992 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Dlugacz, Judy: Biographical Information [flyer], Circa 1993 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Don We Now: A Holiday Concert [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Don We Now: A Holiday Concert [program], 1982 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Don't Bark at My Boyfriend! [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Dubie, Francesca and Clevenson, Deena" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Energy 92.7 FM" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Esprit: New Wave But Love Stays" [flyer], 1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Eichelberger, Ethyl" [flyer], 1987 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Fabulous Ollies of 1981" [program] (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Fierce Pink House" [pamphlet], Circa 1995 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Flower, Robin" [pamphlet], Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Foggy City Dancers: Gay and Lesbian Square Dancing in the Castro" [pamphlet], Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "GALA Choruses Festival 2000" [flyer] (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Gallagher, John Band" [flyer], 1982 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Gay: The San Francisco Gay Freedom Day Marching Band and Twirling Corps, The San Francisco Gay Men's Chorus [program], 1979 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Gay Day" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Gay Games II Cultural Week Inaugural Concert" [flyer], 1986 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Gay Games II Cultural Week Inaugural Concert" [program], 1986 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, D.C." [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, D.C." [order form], Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Gay Musical Celebration, Fourth Annual, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Gay Musical Celebration, Fifth Annual (program), 1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "GGA Summer 1977" (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Gilman, James and Blasdale, Allan: In Concert" [pamplet], 1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Girlyman: Remember Who I Am" [pamphlet], 2004 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Golden Gate Performing Arts Concert Series", 1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Golden Gate Performing Arts Fall '80 Concert Series", 1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Golden Gate Performing Arts Summer Series" [flyer], 1992 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Grant, Beverly In Concert" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Great American Yankee Freedom Band" [pamphlet], Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Harmonic Harvest, S.F. Lesbian / Gay Chorus" [flyer], 1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "Harmonic Harvest: Fall / Winter 82 Concert Series" [program], 1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "Harvey Milk, In Honor of Our Friend", Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Harvey Milk, San Francisco Opera, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Holy Daze, The Choral Majority and The Sisters of Perpetual Indulgence [flyer], 1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - In the Mood, San Francisco Lesbian Chorus [flyer], 1985 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "Kay, Robin Presents Pacific Lesbian and Gay Singers in a Salon Concert" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Kennedy's Children by Robert Patrick [flyer], 1988 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "Kohan, Silvia: Singing Jewish, Latin, Jazz and Blues Styles" [flyer], 1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "It's Love! A Century of Changing Attitudes in American Pop Music" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - La Cage aux Folles [pamphlet], Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "Latino Style!" [flyer], 1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "Lavendar Harmony Band in San Francisco" [flyer], Circa 1979 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Le Desert, San Franciso Gay Men's Chorus [program], 1981 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "Lesbian Concentrate: A Lesbianthology of Songs and Poems" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "Lesbian and Gay Dance Festival" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "Let Freedom Ring" [program], 1987 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "Let's Twist Again III Dance" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "Lovers Too Have a Song to Sing" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Lullabye of Broadway [program], 1984 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - MacKay, Steve and Bibbilly, Ibbilly [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Mambo Italiano, Connie Champagne [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "McDonald, Reginald and Schlactus, Diane" [flyer], 1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "McNight, Sharon, For the Second Annual Christmas Tree Lighting For Ward 5-B" [flyer], 1984 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "McNight, Sharon" [flyer], 1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Michigan Womyn's Music Festival, Fifth Annual [flyer], 1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Michigan Womyn's Music Festival, 7th [flyer], 1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Michigan Womyn's Music Festival, 10th [program], 1985 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Michigan Womyn's Music Festival, 14th [pamphlet], 1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "Monsters of Gay Rock" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "Moon Over Miami Benefit" [program], 1977 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Music and Well Being: A Concert [program], Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Music by Women Composers: A Season of Stars [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Night of 5 Stars [flyer], 1996 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Northbay Pride Music Festival, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "No-tap Invitational Tournament, San Francisco" [program], 1990 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Now Sing With Hearts Aglow [program], 1980 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Now Sing With Hearts Aglow [program], 1983 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "Now Sing With Hearts Aglow Fifth Anniversary Party", 1983 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "Old Follies by Hot Flash!" [flyer], 1983 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "Old Wives' Tales Fifth Birthday Celebration" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - One Hit Wonder, Skateout's Cabaret on Ice Series [program], 2006 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Our Own Kind of Music [program], 1989 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Our Time and Place [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "People's Voice Cafe: Major West-Coast Gay Talents Come East" [flyer], 1983 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "Plutonium Players" [flyer], 1982 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "Power, Will: Orchestra at the Speed of Light" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "Pride Concert of San Francisco, 13th Annual", 1991 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "Pride Concert of San Francisco, 15th Annual" [program], 1993 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "Pride Concert of San Francisco, 16th Annual" [program], 1994 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "Pride Concert of San Francisco, 20th Annual" [flyer], 1998 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "Pride Concert of San Francisco, 24th Annual" [flyer], 2002 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "Quarter Notes" [newsletter], 1986 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Quilt: A Musical Celebration [program], 1994 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Radio Daze [program], 1990 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "Ralph, 'Just for You' with Bob Bendroff at the Piano" [flyer], 1984 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "Randle, Vicki and Millington, June" [flyer], 1980 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "Reighn, David" [flyer], 1982 (Box 7, Folder 4)